Nichols Slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Nichols Slides
2.1.2.4.28
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1411
- Nichols Slides, 2.1.2.4.28
  - Railroad tracks en route from Tacoma to Washington State, circa early 1900s; 37; 42; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  - On the road to the National Park Inn, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 38; 44; 3x4 color (Box 1411)
  Box 1412
- Nichols Slides, 2.1.2.4.28
  - National Park Inn, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 1; 45; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Club house, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 2; 46; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Interior of club house, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 3; 47; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Leaving the inn for the Camp of the Clouds, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 4; 50; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - On Paradise Road below glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 5; 51; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Below Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 6; 52; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Group picture at Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 7; 53; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Government Road, Ricksecker Point, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 8; 54; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Mount Rainier from Ricksecker Point, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 9; 55; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Ghost trees and Mount Rainier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 10; 58; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Paradise Park from upper point of road, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 11; 60; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Avalanche lilies, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 12; 61; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Avalanche lilies, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 13; 62; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Camp of the Clouds, Heather Slope, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 14; 63; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Wild heliotrope, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 15; 65; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Mount Rainier framed, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 16; 66; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Camp of the Clouds and Mount Rainier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 17; 67; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Shooting stars, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 18; 68; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Coasting, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 19; 69; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Paradise Glacier above falls, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 20; 70; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Stevens Glacier and east end of Tatoosh Range, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 21; 71; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Altavista and Tatoosh, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 22; 72; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - East side of Mount Rainier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 23; 75; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 24; 76; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Crevasse in Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 25; 77; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Cascades in Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 26; 78; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - In a crevasse, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 27; 80; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Measuring the flow, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 28; 81; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Climbing the Gibraltar Chute, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 29; 82; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Nearing the summit, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 30; 83; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Inside the crater, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 31; 84; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Indian basket grass, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 32; 85; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Climbing Unicorn Peak in Tatoosh, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 33; 86; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - On the trail to Van Trump Park, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 34; 87; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Comet Falls, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 35; 89; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  - Philemon Beecher Van Trump, first to climb Mount Rainier, circa early 1900s; 36; 90; 3x4 color (Box 1412)
  Box 1413
- Nichols Slides, 2.1.2.4.28
  - Crevasse in Tahoma Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 1; 93; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Indian Henry’s Trail, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 2; 94; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - White rhododendrons, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 3; 95; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Indian Henry’s hunting ground, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 4; 96; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Mount Rainier from Indian Henry’s, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 5; 97; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Tent Hotel at Indian Henry’s, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 6; 98; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Sunset at Indian Henry’s, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 7; 99; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Sierra Club campfire, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Mount Rainier, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Mount Rainier, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Mount Rainier, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - View from ridge, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Stevens Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Sierra Club on Nisqually Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Tahoma Glacier, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Registering at park entrance, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Horseshoe Curve, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Resting on slope in Van Trump Park, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1413)
  - Indian basket grass, Mount Rainier National Park, Washington State, circa early 1900s; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1413)